http://playtheguitar.com/privacy/

playtheguitar.com
https://www.namegala.com
johnnie@topsmedia.com
Privacy policy
Your PrivacyYour privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.Third Party CookiesThird Party ad servers or ad networks may use cookies to track users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies. NameGala.com has no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers.Collection Of Personal InformationWhen visiting NameGala.com, the IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.Links To Third Party WebsitesWe have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own.Changes To This Privacy StatementThe contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion.
